[
  {
    "question": "Alex asked his mother which of the following is not a prime number.",
    "options": [
      "31",
      "61",
      "71",
      "91"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "If the decorated shells represent prime numbers and the plain shells represent composite numbers, which of the following numbers is likely to be prime?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "17",
      "20",
      "15"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Alex challenged Jordon to tell which of the following is a composite number.",
    "options": [
      "81",
      "37",
      "17",
      "19"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The children were asked to tell, which of the following pairs is an example of twin primes?",
    "options": [
      "(5, 7)",
      "(11, 13)",
      "(17, 19)",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Their next question was to solve and tell: What is the smallest 3-digit prime number?",
    "options": [
      "103",
      "101",
      "109",
      "113"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Alex asked his mother, which of the following numbers is a three-digit prime number?",
    "options": [
      "237",
      "331",
      "428",
      "519"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Jordan wanted her mother to tell him, what is the smallest prime number greater than 700.",
    "options": [
      "701",
      "703",
      "707",
      "709"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Alex and Jordan were stuck in finding out which of the following is a prime number.",
    "options": [
      "121",
      "81",
      "1331",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley asked them to consider the following statements:<br> (i) All prime numbers are odd numbers. <br>(ii) There are only three single-digit prime numbers. <br>(iii) There are infinitely many prime numbers. <br>(iv) A prime number has only two factors.<br> Which of the following statements is true?",
    "options": [
      "(i) and (iv)",
      "(ii), (iii) and (iv)",
      "(iii) and (iv)",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Alexa asked Jordan, can he tell which of the following numbers is a composite number that can be expressed as the product of two distinct prime numbers?",
    "options": [
      "35",
      "47",
      "67",
      "89"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley asked her children to tell what is the smallest composite number that is the product of three distinct prime numbers.",
    "options": [
      "24",
      "30",
      "42",
      "48"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley asked Jordon what number is formed by multiplying the first three prime numbers.",
    "options": [
      "50",
      "40",
      "30",
      "20"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "A two-digit number 9A is a prime number. Find the value of A.",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "1",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley asked them, which of the following numbers is a composite number.",
    "options": [
      "101",
      "127",
      "149",
      "187"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley told both of them to answer: How many twin prime pairs are there between 50 and 100?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley gave them different pairs of shells and asked them to identify the twin primes among the given pair of numbers:",
    "options": [
      "(1, 3)",
      "(3, 5)",
      "(13, 19)",
      "(1, 2)"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "If the decorated shells represent prime numbers and the plain shells represent composite numbers, which of the following numbers is likely to be composite?",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "7",
      "10"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Shirley asked Alex to tell how many number of factors 323 has:",
    "options": [
      "No prime factors",
      "Four prime factors",
      "Two prime factors",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Jordan asked Alex, can he tell which of the following is a prime number.",
    "options": [
      "117",
      "147",
      "149",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "At the end, Shirley asked Alex and Jordan to tell which of the following pairs of numbers is a pair of twin primes?",
    "options": [
      "(53, 55)",
      "(61, 63)",
      "(71, 73)",
      "(89, 91)"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  }
]
